http://www.waferseals.com/privacy-policy.php

| Cart Preview U
There are no items in your cart. Continue adding items.
Privacy Policy
Can't find an answer to your question? Click here to Contact Us.
How We Use Your Personal Information
WaferSeals.com does not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information to any company or organization. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release specific information about you, your company, or your account to comply with any valid legal process such as search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order.
We will never use your personally identifiable information to place you on any mailing list that does not belong to WaferSeals.com’s parent company, Brimar Industries, Inc. If you choose to subscribe, we will enroll you to a promotional email list to receive discount offers and special deals. We may also send our customers notifications and direct mailing pieces about products or events that we think may be of interest to them.
We may contact you about your account status, to confirm your registration, or regarding changes to the WaferSeals.com Terms & Conditions or Privacy Policy.
Since we do not track you across third-party websites, we do not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals.
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any
feedback about these sites.
When We Collect Your Personal Information
You may visit WaferSeals.com anonymously. However, we may request personally identifiable information from you in connection with your use of our web site. Our policy is to collect personally identifiable information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us, including when you:
register for an account;
place an order;
subscribe to our newsletter;
respond to a survey;
enter a contest; or
fill out a form.
What Personal Information We Request
When we request information from you in accordance to our policies outlined above, we may ask for personally identifiable information including your:
name;
email address;
mailing address;
phone number;
credit card information; or
company information.
How Personal Information Is Secured
Your information is protected by secure firewalls (communication management computers specially designed to keep information secure and inaccessible by other Internet users).
You’re safe while you shop; and if you choose to store your personal information with us, it’s always secure and protected by your own password.
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, Brimar Industries has put in place advanced and appropriate physical, electronic, testing, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure all the information we collect. Total security includes firewalls, intruder detection, testing, and physical security.
Although we take careful measures to secure both your information and our physical premises, “perfect security” does not exist on the internet; and our efforts in this regard must necessarily be limited by what is practical in light of our equipment and technology.
How We Use Credit Card Information
Sensitive/credit information is transferred to our secure server using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. The only people who have access to your credit card information are banking institutions and their intermediaries. The website and hosting company do not store the information. All the information is received encrypted and remains encrypted.
How We Use Cookies
Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to allow you to use our site’s functionality, including to:
help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart;
understand and save your preferences for future visits; or
keep track of advertisements.
If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service at 800-274-6271.
Trusted third-party vendors use cookies to provide functionality on this website as well as to provide their own services and advertising. You may opt out of third party cookie usage by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page.
Your Rights & Choices
The California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) provides California residents with rights regarding their personal information. You have the right to request a copy of your personal information we have collected in the past twelve months, or for that information to be deleted. We will only deny deletion requests if the information is necessary for us or our third-party vendors to provide the goods or services that you requested when providing that personal information or if we are restricted from doing so due to any other legal obligation. To request your information or its deletion, please call 800-274-6271 or complete our contact form. Please allow up to 45 days for a response. We will not deny service to, alter pricing for, or otherwise discriminate against those who exercise their CCPA rights.
More Information
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information in the footer at the bottom of our site.
Help Pages
Track Your Order
Forgot Password
Contact Us
About Us
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Return Policy
Brimar Industries, Inc.
Brimar Industries 64 Outwater Lane, Garfield NJ 07026 | Phone: 800-274-6271 | Fax: 800-279-6897 | sales@waferseals.com
© 1988-2020 Brimar Industries, Inc.,
All Rights Reserved
X
